Addison Moore

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/addison-moore **Github**: www.github.com/addison912 **Website**: http://www.addisonmoore.me

I'm a freelance full stack engineer, born and raised in the Bay Area. I enjoy camping, board games, cryptocurrency and building full stack applications. Over the past year I've worked with clients to build and deploy well designed websites with simple and intuitive CMS. I also designed and built proprietary trading platforms for cryptocurrency and prediction markets.

SKILLS

Languages: Javascript, Typescript, Python, HTML5, CSS3, French

Frameworks and Libraries: React, React-Native, Scss, Emotion, Babel, Webpack **Backend**: Node.js, Express, Linux, MongoDB, Django, PostgreSQL, OAuth, JWT, NGINX

Version Control and Workflow Management: AGILE, Git, Asana, Trello

Design: Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Sketch, Figma

EXPERIENCE

Freelance / Full Stack Developer

MAY 2020 - PRESENT, SAN FRANCISCO

Over the past year, I've worked as a freelance full stack developer building websites and custom content management systems for clients in a variety of industries. I built OracleInsights a full stack trading platform that provides insights on negative risk opportunities on PredictIt and Augur trading platforms. I also built 38 North, a platform that automates cryptocurrency arbitrage trading between US and South Korean cryptocurrency markets.

Quantum Metric / Software Engineer, Customer Success Team

JULY 2019 - MAY 2020, SAN FRANCISCO

- Primary engineer servicing over \$5M in contracts for brands such as Lululemon, Western Union, eBay, Stubhub, Silicon Valley Bank, and CSAA Insurance.
- · Wrote clean and readable Javascript to gather analytics data and help brands measure their KPIs.
- Worked with top brands to implement Quantum Metric on their digital platforms.
- Works with stakeholders across multiple teams (Product, UX, Fraud Prevention) to understand each teams needs and write quality code to ensure accurate data is provided.

The Bosco / Product Designer, SF Operations Manager

JUNE 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2018, SAN FRANCISCO

- Designed and built custom digital experiences for our clients and core products for The Bosco.
- Lead designer on new core products including the Bosco Lite and Multicam. These products generated over \$10M in revenue for The Bosco during my time there.
- Designed over 50 highly custom digital experiences for brands such as Viacom, Tommy Hilfiger, Facebook, and Sephora.
- Launched the Bosco's San Francisco office. Hired and managed the SF team which consisted of at least 10 operations assistants and event staff throughout my tenure.

EDUCATION

California State University of Monterey Bay

AUGUST 2007 - MAY 2012, SEASIDE, CA

Bachelor's Degree - Visual and Public Art Major, Digital Art and 3D Design

General Assembly

NOVEMBER 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019, SAN FRANCISCO

General Assembly - Web Development Immersive - 4 month full time program

Online certificates and courses:

University of Michigan: Python Data Structures

Frontend Masters: Intermediate React, Typescript, Git In-Depth, Full Stack for Frontend Engineers, Intro to

containers, Networking and Streams, Complete Intro to Vue

Coursera, Udemy: AGILE bootcamp, Beginning Game Programming with C#